Guide to the Alice Fong Yu Papers
Stanford University. Libraries.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Alice Fong Yu papers
1918-2000
1960-1989
SC0872
Yu, Alice Fong
28 Linear feet
These papers document Alice Fong Yu’s lifelong commitment to teaching and her role as a Bay Area Chinese American community leader. Included are files Yu maintained during her career with the San Francisco Unified School District; Yu’s coursework from the speech therapy program at U.C. Berkeley; professional and family correspondence; biographical materials and clippings that highlight many of Yu’s various professional and civic achievements; photograph albums and scrapbooks; administrative materials and publications relating to the Square and Circle Club, the Chinese Historical Society of America, and Berkeley Community Church; and various publications relating to Chinese and Chinese American interests and history.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives Green Library 557 Escondido Mall Stanford, CA 94305-6064 Email: specialcollections@stanford.edu Phone: (650) 725-1022 URL: http://library.stanford.edu/spc
Administrative Information
Information about Access
This collection is open for research.
Biographical/Historical Sketch
Alice Fong Yu (1905-2000) was recruited as the first Chinese American teacher in San Francisco by Commodore Stockton Elementary upon completion of her studies at San Francisco Teachers College in 1926. Inspired by her experiences with her son who was born with cerebral palsy, Yu returned to school in the 1950s and obtained a credential in special education and speech therapy from U.C. Berkeley. With her certification, Yu worked as a speech therapist throughout San Francisco schools until her retirement in 1970. In 1996 San Francisco renamed the nation’s first Chinese-immersion program the Alice Fong Yu School in her honor. In addition to her work as an educator, Yu was very active in many Chinatown organizations. She was a founding member of both the Square and Circle Club and the Chinese Historical Society of America.
Description of the Collection
These papers document Alice Fong Yu’s lifelong commitment to teaching and her role as a Bay Area Chinese American community leader. Included are files Yu maintained during her career with the San Francisco Unified School District; Yu’s coursework from the speech therapy program at U.C. Berkeley; professional and family correspondence; biographical materials and clippings that highlight many of Yu’s various professional and civic achievements; photograph albums and scrapbooks; administrative materials and publications relating to the Square and Circle Club, the Chinese Historical Society of America, and Berkeley Community Church; and various publications relating to Chinese and Chinese American interests and history.
Access Terms
Chinese Historical Society of America.; San Francisco Unified School District.; Square and Circle Club (San Francisco, Calif.); University of California, Berkeley --Students.; Yu, Alice Fong; Chinese American women.; Chinese Americans.
Collection Contents
- Papers
  - Bulletin of the Chinese Historical Society of America, 1960s-1980s (1 of 5) (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Bulletin of the Chinese Historical Society of America, 1960s-1980s (2 of 5) (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Bulletin of the Chinese Historical Society of America, 1960s-1980s (3 of 5) (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Bulletin of the Chinese Historical Society of America, 1960s-1980s (4 of 5) (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Bulletin of the Chinese Historical Society of America, 1960s-1980s (5 of 5) (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Chinese Historical Society - History, 1966-1968 and undated (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Chinese Historical Society - Yu’s Membership Cards, 1967-1969 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Chinese Historical Society - Member Rosters, 1975 and undated (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Chinese Historical Society - Meeting Reports and Minutes, 1963-1966 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Chinese Historical Society - Announcements and Programs, 1965-1979 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Chinese Historical Society - Event Planning, circa 1975 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Chinese Historical Society - Tenth Anniversary, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Chinese Historical Society - “Nevada Centennial Salute to Chinese Pioneers," 1964 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Chinese Historical Society - Constitution, Bylaws, Membership, Activities, Press Releases, etc., 1964-1983 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Chinese Historical Society - Legal Documents, 1965-1982 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Chinese Historical Society - Alice Fong Yu Testimonial Dinner, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Chinese Historical Society - Photograph Collection Guide and Museum Exhibit Information, 1967-1978 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Chinese Historical Society - Notes/Speeches, 1971-1983 and undated (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Chinese Historical Society - Clippings, circa 1941-1975 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Chinese Historical Society of America. The Life, Influence, and the Role of the Chinese in the United States, 1776-1960: Proceedings, Papers of the National Conference Held at the University of San Francisco, July 10, 11, 12, 1975. San Francisco: The Society, 1976. (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Chinese Historical Society - Photographs, 1966-1974 and undated (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Chinese Historical Society - Photographs, 1967 and undated (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Chinese Historical Society Photographs - Presentation of membership scroll to President Lyndon Johnson, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Chinese Historical Society - Weaverville Joss House Centennial, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Chinese Historical Society - Correspondence, 1964-1965 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Chinese Historical Society - Correspondence, 1967-1973 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Chinese Historical Society - Correspondence, 1974 (1 of 3) (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Chinese Historical Society - Correspondence, 1974 (2 of 3) (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Chinese Historical Society - Correspondence, 1974 (3 of 3) (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Chinese Historical Society - Correspondence, 1975-1977 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Chinese Historical Society - Correspondence, 1980-1987 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Chinese Historical Society of America. Chinese America: History and Perspectives, 1988. San Francisco, CA: Chinese Historical Society of America, 1988. (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Chinese Historical Society - California Historic Landmark Project, 1965-1974 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Chinese Historical Society - John Day, Oregon Historic Landmark Project, 1972-1974 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Chinese Historical Society of America - Correspondence and copy of San Francisco Chinese Community Citizens' Survey and Fact Finding Committee. Report. San Francisco: printed by H.J. Carle, 1969. (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - California Historical Society, 1965-1983 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - California and American West - History and Research Materials, 1956-1975 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - California (Nevada County) - History and Research Materials, circa 1970s (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Hawaii Chinese History Center, 1971-1983 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Chinese and Chinese American - Research Material, circa 1950s-1990s (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Square and Circle Club - Correspondence, circa 1970s (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Square and Circle Club - Square Circular Newsletter, 1965-1992 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Square and Circle Club - Miscellaneous, circa 1970s (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Square and Circle Club 65th Anniversary Dinner - Photographs (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Square and Circle Club of San Francisco: A Chinese Women’s Culture. 1987 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Chinese Digest (1 of 3), 1935-1936 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Chinese Digest (2 of 3), 1937 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Chinese Digest (3 of 3), 1938-1939 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Chinatown News (1 of 4), 1976-1977 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Chinatown News (2 of 4), 1977 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Chinatown News (3 of 4), 1977-1978 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Chinatown News (4 of 4), 1978-1979 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Chinese News, 1940-1941 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Amerasia Journal, 1977-1978 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Amerasia Journal, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Chinese Pub-Title Unknown, undated (1 of 3) (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Chinese Pub-Title Unknown, undated (2 of 3) (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Chinese Pub-Title Unknown, undated (3 of 3) (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - China Aircrafter, 1945 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - This Month in the East Bay, 1970s-1980s (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - San Francisco Chinatown, circa 1969-1972 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - San Francisco Chinatown on Parade in Picture and Story, 1961 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Rice Bowl Fashion Show, 1941-1944 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Chinese Community Event Programs, 1971-1989 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Birthday/Wedding/Celebration Programs, 1970s-1980s (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - E Clampus Vitus Banquet, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous Pamphlets, Undated (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous Chinese Language Material, Undated (Box 7, Folder 6)
    Includes: copy of Augsut 1966 Ming Bao Monthly Magazine; copy of July 1966 MIng Bao Monthly Magazine; Ali-shan Song; brief account of Chinese Historical Society: It's History and Activities, circa 1974; Chinese/English flyer about Chinese Historical Society, 1963.
  - Miscellaneous Chinese Language Material (2 of 4), Undated (Box 7, Folder 7)
    Includes: donation receipts (Yu's) to China War Relief Association, circa 1930s, and to the Chinese aviation program; several packets of donation receipts forom the Kuomintang, 1927; a K.M.T. party card with Yu's name and picture in it, circa 1928; prayer in Chinese, 1971, apparently someone's corrected homework; draft proposal for protection of the overseas Chinese, circa 1960s; Chinese class assignments, circa 1970s.
  - Miscellaneous Chinese Language Material (3 of 4), Undated (Box 7, Folder 8)
    Includes: letter to Yu, 1973 Jan; form letter from Sun Yat Sen Assoc, Sacramento, 1972; song in Chinese; chart listing proper terms for relatives; 1989 anniversary and birthday card.
  - Miscellaneous Chinese Language Material (4 of 4), Undated (Box 7, Folder 9)
    Funeral programs for two members of the Yu family, 1990s.
  - Miscellaneous Chinese Language Correspondence, Undated (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Chinese Paper Decorations, Undated (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Speeches re China given by C. H. Lowe, 1957 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Miscellaneous Mementos, Undated (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Berkeley Community Church (1 of 2), Undated (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Berkeley Community Church (2 of 2), Undated (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Chinese Congregational Church 100th Anniversary, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Church Women United, 1977-1986 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Pacific and Asian American Ecumenical Convocation, 1982 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Chinese Christian Conference Programs, 1941-1958 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Religious Material - Miscellaneous, circa 1970s-1980s (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Federation of Chinese Clubs, 1939 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Chinese Culture Foundation, circa 1970s-1980s (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Asian Pacific American Coalition Material, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Older Women’s League, 1987-1988 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Association of Chinese Americans Newsletter, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Chinese for Affirmative Action Newsletter, 1980-1982 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - The Yoke Choy Life, Undated (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - World Today Magazine, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Prism Magazine, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Newsletters-Miscellaneous Organizations, 1956-1988 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Dynasty Magazine, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Japan Trip Mementos, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - USSR Program, 1967 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - China Trip Mementos, October-November, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - San Francisco Examiner Distinguished Ten Awards, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - “Directory of Significant 20th Century American Minority Women” Nomination, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Alice Fong Yu - Awards and Honors, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Alice Fong Yu - Biographical (1 of 2), 1990s-2000 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Alice Fong Yu - Biographical (2 of 2), 1970s-1980s (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Alice Fong Yu - Civic Activities and Charitable Contributions, 1976-1983 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Yu Family Information and Newsletter, 1954-1960 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Stamps and First Day Covers (1 of 2), Undated (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Stamps and First Day Covers (1 of 2), Undated (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Blank Stationery, Undated (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Restaurant Directories, 1977-1981 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Appointment Calendars, 1964-1983 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Appointment Calendars, 1986-1992 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Notebooks, Undated (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Address Book, Undated (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Autograph Album, Undated (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Maps, Undated (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Paintings, 1919 and undated (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Vallejo High School Coursework and Material, 1918-1924 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Vallejo High School 50 Year Reunion, 1973-1986 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - UC Berkeley - Education 112 (1 of 2), 1957 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - UC Berkeley - Education 112 (2 of 2), 1957 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - UC Berkeley - Education 164, 1954 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - UC Berkeley - Education 200C, 1957 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - UC Berkeley - Education 210, 1956-1957 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - UC Berkeley - Education 211B, 1951-1957 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - UC Berkeley - Education 216B/224, 1956-1957 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - UC Berkeley - English 131, 1957 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - UC Berkeley - Speech 134, circa 1954 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - UC Berkeley - Miscellaneous Education Coursework (1 of 2), circa 1950s (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - UC Berkeley - Miscellaneous Education Coursework (2 of 2), circa 1950s (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous Education Notes (1 of 3), circa 1957 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous Education Notes (2 of 3), 1950s (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous Education Notes (3 of 3), Undated (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Educational Pamphlets and Brochures, Undated (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Educational Pamphlets and Brochures, Undated (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Educational Pamphlets and Brochures, Undated (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - American History Resources, circa 1950s (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Teacher’s Manuals, 1941-1945 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Student Workbook, 1952 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Speech Education Materials, 1940s-1960s (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - SFUSD - Career Files, 1920s-1990s (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - SFUSD - Handouts, Lectures, Meetings, etc., 1940s-1960s (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - SFUSD - Newsletters and Notes, Undated (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Commodore Stockton School Dedication, 1958 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Alice Fong Yu School Dedication, January 1996 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - The Association of Chinese Teachers (TACT), circa 1980s (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Education - Miscellaneous Publications and Newsletters (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - School Event Programs, Undated (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - School Commencement Programs, 1959-1980 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Mills College Continuing Studies, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Chancellor Hilary Hsu’s Speech at Laney College, 3/5/1984 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Books:
    - Bailey, Andrew. A Day in the Life of the World. (Box 14)
    - Winter, Roberta H. Once More Around Jericho: The Story of the U.S Center for World Mission. (Box 14)
    - Hunt, Gladys M. Does Anyone Here Know God? Stories of Women Who Do. (Box 14)
    - Reese, D. Vaughan. The "Jesus Family" in Communist China. (Box 14)
    - Peter Pauper Press. America, the Beautiful: Being a Collection of Documents and Speeches Which Have Laid the Cornerstone of Democracy for the United States of America. (Box 14)
    - Pape, Dorothy R. In Search of God's Ideal Woman: A Personal Examination of the New Testament. (Box 14)
    - Holy Bible. (Box 14)
  - Books:
    - Creel, Herrlee Glessner. Chinese Thought, from Confucius to Mao Tsê-Tung. (Box 15)
    - Chinn, Thomas W. Bridging the Pacific: San Francisco Chinatown and Its People. (Box 15)
    - Painter, Charlotte, and Pamela Valois. Gifts of Age: Portraits and Essays of 32 Remarkable Women. (Box 15)
    - Mark, Diane Mei Lin, and Ginger Chih. A Place Called Chinese America. (Box 15)
    - Ketchum, Richard M. The American Heritage Book of Great Historic Places. (Box 15)
    - Himmelwright, Abraham Lincoln Artman. The San Francisco Earthquake and Fire: A Brief History of the Disaster; a Presentation of Facts and Resulting Phenomena. (Box 15)
    - Smith, May Hurlbert. Stanford "from the Foothills to the Bay". [The Story of Stanford.] (Box 15)
  - Books:
    - University of California, Berkeley. 1924 Blue and Gold: A Record of the College Year 1922-1923. (Box 16)
    - Kent, Rockwell. World Famous Paintings. New York: Wise. (Box 16)
    - United Nations Conference, San Francisco, California, April 25 to June 26, 1945. (Box 16)
    - Shepherd, Charles Reginald. Lim Yik Choy, The Story of a Chinese Orphan. (Box 16)
    - Sparks, Theresa A. China Gold. (Box 16)
  - Correspondence - 1920s (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence - 1930s (1 of 2) (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence - 1930s (2 of 2) (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence - 1940s (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence - 1950-1955 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence - 1956-1957 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence - 1958-1960 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence - 1961-1965 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence - 1966 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence - 1967 (1 of 2) (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence - 1967 (2 of 2) (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence - 1968-1969 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence - 1970 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence - 1971 (1 of 2) (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence - 1971 (2 of 2) (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence - 1972 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence - 1973 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence - 1974 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence - 1975 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence - 1976 (1 of 6) (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence - 1976 (2 of 6) (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence - 1976 (3 of 6) (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence - 1976 (4 of 6) (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence - 1976 (5 of 6) (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence - 1976 (6 of 6) (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence - 1977 (1 of 4) (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence - 1977 (2 of 4) (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence - 1977 (3 of 4) (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence - 1977 (4 of 4) (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence - 1978 (1 of 2) (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence - 1978 (2 of 2) (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence - 1979 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence - 1980 (1 of 2) (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence - 1980 (2 of 2) (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence - 1981 (1 of 2) (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence - 1981 (2 of 2) (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence - 1982 (1 of 2) (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence - 1982 (2 of 2) (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence - 1983 (1 of 2) (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence - 1983 (2 of 2) (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence - 1984 (1 of 3) (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence - 1984 (2 of 3) (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence - 1984 (3 of 3) (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence - 1985 (1 of 5) (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence - 1985 (2 of 5) (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence - 1985 (3 of 5) (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence - 1985 (4 of 5) (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence - 1985 (4 of 5) (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence - 1986 (1 of 2) (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence - 1986 (2 of 2) (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence - 1987 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence - 1988 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence - 1989 (1 of 3) (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence - 1989 (2 of 3) (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence - 1989 (3 of 3) (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence - 1990s (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence - Undated (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence - Santa Letters (Box 24)
  - Photographs, Undated (Box 25)
  - Photographs - Small Studio Portraits, undated (1 of 2) (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Photographs - Small Studio Portraits, undated (2 of 2) (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Photographs - Studio Portraits, undated (1 of 3) (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Photographs - Studio Portraits, undated (2 of 3) (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Photographs - Studio Portraits, undated (3 of 3) (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Photographs - Group Shots, undated (1 of 2) (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Photographs - Group Shots, undated (2 of 2) (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Photographs - Family, undated (1 of 2) (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Photographs - Family, undated (2 of 2) (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Photographs - Miscellaneous, undated (1 of 2) (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Photographs - Miscellaneous, undated (2 of 2) (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Photographs - Slides, Undated (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Photograph Albums and Scrapbooks (Box 27)
  - Photograph Albums and Scrapbooks (Box 28)
  - Photograph Albums and Scrapbooks (Box 29)
  - Scrapbooks (Box 30)
  - Photograph Albums and Scrapbooks (Box 31)
  - Scrapbooks (Box 32)
  - Memorabilia/Chinese Souvenirs (Box 33)
  - Oversize:
    - Photographs - Museum Opening (Box 34)
    - Photographs - Calaveras and Humboldt Counties (Box 34)
    - Photographs - UC campus (Box 34)
    - Photographs - Large Portraits (Box 34)
    - Miscellaneous Oversize Resolutions and Certificates - Nevada Centennial and Chinese Historical Society (Box 34)
  - Oversize:
    - Visual Teaching Aids - Photographs/Posters (Box 35)
  - Oversize:
    - Stanford Area Chinese Club (Box 36)
    - Cal Folder Containing Religious Case Studies (Box 36)
    - Les Nouvelles De Moscou Newspaper, 1965 (Box 36)
    - Chinese Women of America Calendar 1985 (Box 36)
    - Mei Lan-Fang - Pacific Coast Tour Program (Box 36)
    - Cruise Programs and Photographs (Box 36)
    - Chinese Program (Box 36)
    - California Living (San Francisco Examiner), Dec. 4, 1966 (Box 36)
    - U.S. Senator Alan Cranston Reports to Californians, January 1982 (Box 36)
    - Chinese Masterworks in the National Palace Museum - Ming Porcelain (Box 36)
    - Book - Reflections in Pike Place Markets (Box 36)
  - News Clippings (Box 37)
  - News Clippings - Chinese (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - News Clippings - Miscellaneous (1 of 6) (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - News Clippings - Miscellaneous (2 of 6) (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - News Clippings - Miscellaneous (3 of 6) (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - News Clippings - Miscellaneous (4 of 6) (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - News Clippings - Miscellaneous (5 of 6) (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - News Clippings - Miscellaneous (5 of 6) (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - News Clippings - Yu - Biographical (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - News Clippings - Yu - Family (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Miscellaneous Notes, Undated (Box 39)